But Sir, ICICI becomes
part, I will
keep it in the Nifty component, so a
reversal is ready from here, it will start,
currently it is moving around 34,
if I take it, then the number of 1134 is
a support for you, not out, the
number of 1134 is a support, below you, you have to
maintain a stop loss of ₹190 backup and
press the mind inside it, now you
can close in two layers, one you can bank,
second you will get a closing level of 1175 to 1190 above 1175, find that
place and
you have to maintain the stop loss of 100090,
near 15th November, when the rally starts,
after 15-18,
there you have to cut for one to two
months,
keep a target of 60 to 90 days within two months, two to three
months because India is showing a target of up to 1350, let
me take it at 1200  If I have kept it then I am
making it and those targets will be achieved, I have to stay put and
not exit
because the day of exit is over, I had to exit at ₹1280
earlier but now I cannot exit because the
time is over because
we trade according to time, so the time is from
10th to 18th, I have to exit for eight more days, it
may not go down because 1000 90
is that level which,
leaving aside the proge, in the technical chart also
it has taken tremendous support at 1120
and has been supported multiple times, a
stop of 1000 90 has been given, so it is possible that the
levels will be achieved and profit will also be made